gaymanicus.com 2009-06-19

# GAYMANICUS - Gay Muscle, Jock and Latino Free Gay Porn Galleries updated daily

**Gaymanicus.com Privacy Policy**

Email Privacy Policy 

We have created this email privacy policy to demonstrate our firm commitment to your privacy and the protection of your information.

Why did you receive an email from us? 

If you received a mailing from us, (a) your email address is either listed with us as someone who has expressly shared this address for the purpose of receiving information in the future ("opt-in"), or (b) you have registered or purchased or otherwise have an existing relationship with us. We respect your time and attention by controlling the frequency of our mailings. 

How we protect your privacy 

We use security measures to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of data used by our system.

_ Sharing and Usage  _

We will never share, sell, or rent individual personal information with anyone without your advance permission or unless ordered by a court of law. Information submitted to us is only available to employees of Alternative Media Group LLC and its network of companies,  managing this information for purposes of contacting you or sending you emails based on your request for information and to contracted service providers for purposes of providing services relating to our communications with you.

How can you stop receiving email from us? 

Each email sent contains an easy, automated way for you to cease receiving email from us, or to change your expressed interests. If you wish to do this, simply follow the instructions at the end of any email.

** If you have received unwanted, unsolicited email sent via this system or purporting to be sent via this system, please forward a copy of that email with your comments to  [ support@gaymanicus.com](mailto:support@gaymanicus.com).**

** Privacy Policy Changes**

This policy was created on April 14, 2008
